So what is webpack?
Czym wic jest Webpack?
Webpack is a bundler but it actually is more than that, a bundler alone would just concatenate files, webpack
Webpack jest pakerem, ale tak naprawd jest czym wicej, tylko pakiet bundlerowy po prostu czy pliki, dziaa w pakiecie
does that
sieci Web,
but it also allows you to optimize your files and you hook in various plugins and so-called loaders
ale pozwala rwnie na optymalizacj plikw i przechwytuje rne wtyczki i tak zwane programy adujce, aby
to also transform your files
rwnie przeksztaca pliki i przykad
and for example transpile next generation javascript to current generation javascript. But in its core,
przenie javascript nastpnej generacji do javascript obecnej generacji. Ale w swojej istocie, ide
the idea behind webapck is to have multiple javascript, css, image, whatever files and bundle them together.
webapck jest posiadanie wielu javascript, css, image, dowolnych plikw i pakowanie ich razem.
It analyzes connections between these files like imports and then bundles everything together, allows
Analizuje poczenia midzy tymi plikami, takie jak import, a nastpnie czy wszystko razem, umoliwia
you to optimize it
optymalizacj i,
and as I said, allows you to also run some additional logic to transform your code or do whatever you
jak ju powiedziaem, pozwala rwnie uruchomi dodatkow logik, aby przeksztaci kod lub zrobi, co trzeba
need to do with it.
z nim zrobi.
This is what webpack does and webpack is the de-facto standard for setting up projects these days.
Tak wanie dziaa pakiet internetowy i pakiet internetowy jest de facto standardem do tworzenia projektw w tych dniach.
That's why we'll also use it in this module for setting up our own react workflow and project.
Dlatego te uyjemy go w tym module do konfigurowania naszego wasnego przepywu pracy i projektu.